comradez.net 2010-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Comradez.net

This privacy policy (the " **Privacy Policy** ") is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information and Anonymous Information you submit to us through our Services.

Comradez places great importance in protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to explain the manner in which Comradez collects, uses, and discloses the personal information provided by you as a result of the use of Comradez Site and the content, information and services provided through the Web Site by Comradez.

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION**

In order for you to register as a user on this Site, this Site requires that you provide certain personal information, including, but not limited to, your name and e-mail address. We use this information in order to contact you to provide you with further information about our website and services, as well as for other commercial and or internal purposes such as market research in order to better understand the demographics of our Site visitors and potential customers and partners. We may share this information with our authorized partners and or with third parties who act for or on behalf of us, but we do not otherwise provide or sell any information gathered on this Site to outside vendors. 

**USER TRACKING**

This Site implements a user tracking feature, whereby the activities of each unique visitor to the Site are monitored. This is done regardless of whether the visitor has registered on the Site or is visiting the Site anonymously. If you do not register on this Site or fill in your personal details on any forms, you do remain anonymous and we do not discover your identity. If you do register on this Site, our use of user tracking enables us to identify your future and prior activities on the Site, including your activity before you registered. This includes pages on our Site that you visited. User tracking also allows us to determine through which means you have reached our Site (i.e. which search engines or links) up to one web page back. The purpose of our user tracking is to analyze our visitor's actions in order to improve the user experience of visitors to our Site, as well as to better understand the priorities and interests of our potential customers and partners in order to better suit their needs and increase the efficiency of our sales and marketing processes.

**USE OF COOKIES**

A "cookie" is a small text file transferred by a Web Site to a computer that is browsing the Web Site. Even if you do not register on this Site, upon your first visit to this Site (or subsequent visits if you delete the cookie), a cookie is stored on your computer, which automatically identifies you to the Site. This is done for several technical reasons, including enabling the "User Tracking" described above. In addition, for your convenience, the cookie can "autofill" information on forms on the Site, precluding the need for you to fill out the same information on our registration forms each time you want to access information that requires registration. However, cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user; the only personal information we learn about you is that which you provide to us, as described above. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. In addition, you can delete any cookies that have already been placed on your computer. 

If you choose to enter personal information into your Comradez profile certain information may be displayed to publicly. If you choose to make a post or upload on Comradez, these post or uploads will be displayed publicly along with your avatar, screen name, and a link back to your profile. Comradez also enables site developers to apply badges and access to APIs to collect and display certain information off of the Comradez site. This is includes developers that have recently added interest-based advertising programs, which allows them the ability to track site visitation and then customize advertising content based on that visitation.

**3rd Party Based Advertising**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on comradez.com

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy

**Changes to this policy**

This Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.
